all right everyone I hope you've been
training because it's time for the great
Sonic Underground marathon
you're gonna need oil change you're
gonna be bow away ain't that right Bobby
yeah this guy he's gonna kick all your
asses this is going down today it's
going down it's going down like sock on
the ground good luck everyone but you
won't beat me I've been training hard
for this day we all may be best friends
but I'm not going to come in last place
like a little yet that's the
spirit Sonja challenges are always fun
or when we give it our all
ha ha ha ha ha that's funny you
actually think you're going to beat me
me Knuckles the cool Echidna sorry but
it doesn't work like that you'll
have a better chance being chosen as the
one to suck my balls after this race is
over right glad see everyone is excited
these are the rules we'll go run 50
miles first time did you get the air get
to the end get some chili
dog I'm gonna count down from three and
when I hit you we're all gonna haul ass
5 4 3 2 1 go
[Music]
i won